<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Products on SangMyung</title>
    <link>http://sangmyungtrading.cafe24.com/product/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Products on SangMyung</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 13:39:46 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://sangmyungtrading.cafe24.com/product/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>D758 Motor Purge &amp; Pressurization System</title>
      <link>http://sangmyungtrading.cafe24.com/product/d758/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sangmyungtrading.cafe24.com/product/d758/</guid>
      <description>IECEx, ATEX &amp;amp; INMETRO Certified Purge and Pressurization System for large Electrical Machines.
Features   Global approvals
  Purge flow capacity up to 6,000 Nl/min
  Stable machine pressure with CLAPS technology
  Stainless steel enclosure construction.
  Temperature range -20°C to +55°C
  Description The D758 purge and pressurization system delivers purge flowrates up to 6,000 Nl/min and is ideal for medium to large sized Ex p electrical machines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enclosure Cooling</title>
      <link>http://sangmyungtrading.cafe24.com/product/enclosure-cooling/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sangmyungtrading.cafe24.com/product/enclosure-cooling/</guid>
      <description>IECEx and ATEX Certified vortex coolers for enclosure thermal management
Features   Cooling capacity up to 800W
  IECEx and ATEX Certified
  Cold air from compressed air
  Direct mount through enclosure wall
  Description Thermal management for electrical enclosures should be considered at the design and specification stage. While enclosure heating is relatively straightforward, cooling is more complex and may be required to either remove the heat generated by electrical components or to compensate for high ambient temperatures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fast-track Standard Enclosure Service</title>
      <link>http://sangmyungtrading.cafe24.com/product/fast-track-enslosure-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sangmyungtrading.cafe24.com/product/fast-track-enslosure-service/</guid>
      <description>Using standardised building blocks and automated configuration and design tools, Expo’s Fast-Track service can deliver you tailor-made enclosures within weeks.
Expo manufactures the enclosure to your specifications and delivers to you component certified. If this is an Ex p enclosure, then the purge system will already be installed and tested. The enclosure can then be populated at your facility.
For systems using purge &amp;amp; pressurization, Expo holds populated enclosure certificates for ATEX &amp;amp; IECEx, so it can offer a full certification service on the finished system, giving significant time and cost benefits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fully custom Enclosure Service</title>
      <link>http://sangmyungtrading.cafe24.com/product/fully-custom-enclosure-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sangmyungtrading.cafe24.com/product/fully-custom-enclosure-service/</guid>
      <description>Some projects call for special shapes and sizes of enclosures, non-standard features or very special applications, and may also require input from a Notified Body during the design phase or final certification.
With Expo’s fully custom process, a dedicated engineer will work with you to develop exactly what you need and agree on a detailed budget and project timeline with milestones. As this is a highly flexible service, we can adapt the plan if your project requirements change.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Low Temperature Motor Purge &amp; Pressurization Systems</title>
      <link>http://sangmyungtrading.cafe24.com/product/lowtemperature/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sangmyungtrading.cafe24.com/product/lowtemperature/</guid>
      <description>IECEx, ATEX &amp;amp; INMETRO Certified Purge and Pressurization Systems for Electrical Machines in Very Low Temperature Environments
Features   Certification to -60°C
  Purge flow capacity between 1,000 and 14,000 Nl/min
  Stable machine pressure with CLAPS technology
  Stainless steel enclosure construction
  Description Building on the range of motor purge and pressurization systems for standard temperature, Expo have developed special systems for low temperature service as low as -60oC ambient.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MiniPurge Type X</title>
      <link>http://sangmyungtrading.cafe24.com/product/minipurge-type-x/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sangmyungtrading.cafe24.com/product/minipurge-type-x/</guid>
      <description>Introduction |iIECEx, ATEX &amp;amp; UL certified purge and pressurization systems for Zone 1, Class I Div 1 applications
Features   Global approvals
  Purge flow capacity up to 900 Nl/min
  Leakage Compensation or Continuous Flow
  Stainless steel enclosure construction
  Description Expo’s Minipurge type X range provides a full purge and pressurization solution for electrical enclosures and other equipment installed in Zone 1 or Class I Div 1 hazardous environments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MiniPurge Type Z(Y)</title>
      <link>http://sangmyungtrading.cafe24.com/product/minipurge-type-zy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sangmyungtrading.cafe24.com/product/minipurge-type-zy/</guid>
      <description>IECEx, ATEX &amp;amp; UL certified purge and pressurization systems for Zone 2, Class I Div 2 applications
Features   Global approvals
  Purge flow capacity up to 900 Nl/min
  Leakage Compensation or Continuous Flow
  Stainless steel enclosure construction
  Description Expo’s Minipurge type Z range provides a full purge and pressurization solution for electrical enclosures and other equipment installed in Zone 2 or Class I Div 2 hazardous environments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motor Pre-Start Ventilation Systems (3PV, 5PV, 7PV)</title>
      <link>http://sangmyungtrading.cafe24.com/product/motor-pre-startventilationsystems/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sangmyungtrading.cafe24.com/product/motor-pre-startventilationsystems/</guid>
      <description>IECEx &amp;amp; ATEX certified pre-start ventilation systems for large Ex e &amp;amp; Ex n electrical machines
Features   Certification to +60°C
  Pre-start ventilation flow capacity up to 14,000 Nl/min
  Remote start options
  Stainless steel enclosure construction
  Description Expo’s PV range of pre-start ventilation systems provide essential protection to large non-sparking electric motors. The PV range can deliver pre-start ventilation flow rates of up to 14,000 Nl/min and is ideal for very large sized Ex e and Ex n electrical machines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Purge System Interface Units (MIU/SIU)</title>
      <link>http://sangmyungtrading.cafe24.com/product/purge-system-interface-units-miusiu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sangmyungtrading.cafe24.com/product/purge-system-interface-units-miusiu/</guid>
      <description>IECEx, ATEX &amp;amp; INMETRO Ex d certified solutions for enclosure power and signal isolation.
Features   Global Ex d approvals
  Isolates low power signals and up to 32 A power
  Compatible with MiniPurge &amp;amp; SmartPurge II
  Aluminium construction
  Description Expo’s Interface Units provide switching of power and signals to the pressurized enclosure, using a control signal from the purge system. This capability is required for enclosures installed in Zone 1/21 or Class I/II Div 1 hazardous locations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RoomPressurization Systems RP-Max</title>
      <link>http://sangmyungtrading.cafe24.com/product/room-pressurization-systems-rp-max/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sangmyungtrading.cafe24.com/product/room-pressurization-systems-rp-max/</guid>
      <description>Certified solutions for the pressurization of drillers cabins and analyser houses
 Features    Meets NFPA Class I Div.2 &amp;amp; ATEX Zone 2 standards
  entilation capacity up to 4,700 m3/hr
  Dual redundant fan option
  Roof, wall and in-line mounting options
   Description Expo’s RP-Max-Z room pressurization systems are designed for type Z / Ex pz pressurization in accordance with NFPA496 and ATEX for Class I Div 2 and Zone 2 hazardous areas, making the interior of the room a general-purpose location.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SmartPurgeII</title>
      <link>http://sangmyungtrading.cafe24.com/product/smartpurgeii/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sangmyungtrading.cafe24.com/product/smartpurgeii/</guid>
      <description>IECEx, ATEX &amp;amp; FM certified intelligent purge &amp;amp; pressurization system
Features   Global approvals
  Purge flow capacity up to 540 Nl/min
  Can be configured as Type X, Y or Z purge
  Leakage Compensation or Continuous Flow
  Stainless steel enclosure construction
  Description The SmartPurge II (SP2) is a highly flexible electronic purge and pressurization system suitable for a wide range of flow rates and duties.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
