<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Enclosures on SangMyung</title>
    <link>http://sangmyungtrading.cafe24.com/categories/enclosures/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Enclosures on SangMyung</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 13:39:46 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://sangmyungtrading.cafe24.com/categories/enclosures/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fast-track Standard Enclosure Service</title>
      <link>http://sangmyungtrading.cafe24.com/product/fast-track-enslosure-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sangmyungtrading.cafe24.com/product/fast-track-enslosure-service/</guid>
      <description>Using standardised building blocks and automated configuration and design tools, Expo’s Fast-Track service can deliver you tailor-made enclosures within weeks.
Expo manufactures the enclosure to your specifications and delivers to you component certified. If this is an Ex p enclosure, then the purge system will already be installed and tested. The enclosure can then be populated at your facility.
For systems using purge &amp;amp; pressurization, Expo holds populated enclosure certificates for ATEX &amp;amp; IECEx, so it can offer a full certification service on the finished system, giving significant time and cost benefits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fully custom Enclosure Service</title>
      <link>http://sangmyungtrading.cafe24.com/product/fully-custom-enclosure-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sangmyungtrading.cafe24.com/product/fully-custom-enclosure-service/</guid>
      <description>Some projects call for special shapes and sizes of enclosures, non-standard features or very special applications, and may also require input from a Notified Body during the design phase or final certification.
With Expo’s fully custom process, a dedicated engineer will work with you to develop exactly what you need and agree on a detailed budget and project timeline with milestones. As this is a highly flexible service, we can adapt the plan if your project requirements change.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
